* Mon - Fri: 8:00 am - 4:30 pm

**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  
  
**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  
  
**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  
  
**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  
  
**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  
  
**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  
  
**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  
  
**Warning**: Undefined array key "background\_image" in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **87**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type null in **/home/unitedway/www/www/wp-content/plugins/elementor/includes/conditions.php** on line **90**  

[LIVE UNITED

CLICK HERE TO LEARN MORE](https://unitedwayswi.org/live-united)

[GIVE

CLICK HERE TO LEARN MORE](https://unitedwayswi.org/give)

[ADVOCATE

CLICK HERE TO LEARN MORE](https://unitedwayswi.org/advocate)

[VOLUNTEER

CLICK HERE TO LEARN MORE](https://unitedwayswi.org/volunteer)

Menu

PRIVACY POLICY

**A FIRM COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**                    

Your privacy is a priority for United Way of Southwestern Indiana (“United Way”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) and we want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information relating to you.  This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to all information received by United Way, both online and offline, on any platform, including our website, as well as electronic, written and oral communications.

**UNITED WAY’S COMMITMENT TO OUR DONORS**

United Way will not sell, share or trade donor personal information with any other entity, nor send mailings to you on behalf of other organizations, without your prior consent or except as outlined in this Policy.

**INFORMATION UNITED WAY COLLECTS**

**“Personally Identifiable Information” (“PII”)** is information that tells us who you are, such as name, physical address, and e-mail address, and any other information we collect that is defined as personal or personally identifiable under an applicable law. United Way will collect PII from donors and users (“Visitors”) of our website only if they voluntarily submit such information. Visitors can refuse to supply PII, but it may prevent them from engaging in certain activities and limit their ability to use our website, services or activities we provide.

**“****Usage Information”** is information automatically collected by a web server (which may be hosted by a third party) that a Visitor’s browser makes available when visiting the Site, such as a computer’s IP (Internet Protocol) address or browser type.    

**HOW UNITED WAY PROTECTS YOUR INFORMATION**

United Way uses industry-leading Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration of the information it collects and maintains, both online and offline. All information is stored in a secure database. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although United Way does its best to protect your PII, the security of your personal or sensitive information transmitted to us is not guaranteed. Any transmission of PII or sensitive information is at your own risk. United Way will not be responsible for disclosure of information due to errors in transmission or circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures United Way put in place for your protection.

**Security of Credit Card Information**

United Way uses a variety of safeguards to protect the security of credit card transactions, including encryption, access controls, network firewalls, physical security and other measures.  

**HOW UNITED WAY USES YOUR INFORMATION**

If you provide United Way with personal information, we may enter your PII into our database so we can contact you to obtain your input, provide information about United Way programs and events, show our appreciation, or solicit future contributions.

United Way may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your PII for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Surveys and contests**

From time-to-time United Way may request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information.

**Sharing your information**

Personal information volunteered by donors as part of the donation process is for use by authorized employees, contractors, board members, advisors and volunteers for the purposes stated in this Policy.

There are circumstances where United Way may need to transfer and/or disclose PII to third parties.  Those circumstances include, but are not limited to: disclosure to website consultants and third-party service providers (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential); when we believe disclosure is required by law; to protect the rights, property or personal safety of United Way; or as otherwise set forth herein.  We may also provide your personal information to the agency you have designated as the recipient of your generosity, unless you specifically request anonymity of your donation.

**Cookies or other technologies**

United Way may use other technologies (such as cookies, explained below) to enhance Visitor experience and obtain information about a Visitor’s activities on our Site, such as pages and content viewed, the time and duration of visits and whether a Visitor clicked on a link.  

Cookies used on the Site are “session” cookies, and are used to identify a particular visit to the Site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when a Visitor closes a web browser. Due to Internet communications standards, when Visitors visit the Site, it automatically receives the URL of the web site from which the Visitor came and the web site the Visitor visits when leaving.

Visitors may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to receive an alert when cookies are being sent. Doing so may result in some parts of the Site not functioning properly. Additionally, some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, United Way has no access to or control over these cookies.

**Log files**

Like most standard website servers, United Way may use log files, which include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type and date/time stamp, as well as the number of clicks that help to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  Log files, specifically IP addresses, are not linked to personal information.

**LINKS**

The Site contains links to other websites. United Way is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites and encourages Visitors to review the privacy policies of the other websites before providing them with any personally identifiable data.

**POLICY CHANGES**

United Way reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we do, we will note the most recent date of revision at the top of this policy and post such amended or updated policy on the Site.  A subsequent donation by you will be deemed your agreement that your information may be used in accordance with the new policy.

**VISITOR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION**

If you have questions about this Policy or wish to review, update, correct or delete your information or opt out of receiving future communications, you may contact United Way at 812-422-4100.

United Way of Southwestern Indiana  
318 Main Street, Suite 504  
Evansville, IN  47708  
Phone: [812-422-4100](tel:812-422-4100)

About
-----

Impact
------

Get Involved
------------

Copyright © 2022 United Way of Southwestern Indiana

Web Design by [Kitch & Schreiber](https://www.kitchandschreiber.com/)

MORNING FLIGHT GOLFERS: We are still on for this morning. The ECC and UWSWI staff will monitor the weather for lightning and will make a call as soon as possible. We may have a delay.

##### Thank You For Your Submission

Make Your  
Donation Today
==========================
